(Howard:)Check it out. Mrs. Davis
from Human Resources is here.
(Howard:)She's probably on the lookout
for sexual harassment.
(Raj:)Oh, great. There go my chances
of being sexually harassed.
(Howard:)I heard her husband left her
for a hot, young undergrad.
(Raj:)That's so much better
than the old, ugly ones.
(Mrs Davis:)Mr. Wolowitz, Dr. Koothrappali.
(Howard:)Mrs. Davis, nice to see you.
(Raj:)You know, I recently read
a fascinating article
(Raj:)-On infidelity among penguins.
-Okay.
(Raj:)So if the fact
that your husband left you
(Raj:)makes you feel unattractive, just
remember, penguins get cheated on,
(Raj:)and they're adorable.
(Howard:)It was better when you
couldn't talk to women.